Finding Aid for the Jesse Ely Wills Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- "High Moment," CP
- "The Hills Remember," F, EL
- "I Have Known Many," EL "I Would Give Thanks," EL "In the Day-Coach," J "Incognito," EL
- "The Last Confederate," CP "Lausanne," F "Less Seriously," N "Libraries," N
- JL JL JL %’ • • *J
- "Lightning's Blink," F, EL "The Lights Go Out," N "Love's End," N
- "The Man Who Really Knew," EL "Meditations of a Wasp," N "The Metal from the Ore," EL "Miracle," EL "Misery," J "Misgiving," N
- "Nashville," N
- "Night Windows," F, EL
- "November, 1957," EL
- "Of Many Mockingbirds," N
- "Old Leaves," EL
- "On a Picture of Earth," N
- "On Hearing of the Death of a Friend," CP
- "Once," EL
- "Optimist," J
- "Parable," F, EL "Pictures Out of Frame," EL "Prayer," EL "Premonition," F, EL "Primavera," F, EL "The Proposal," F
- "Question," N
- "Question Mark and Elegy," EL
- "Red," N
- "Red Even," F, EL
- "Rejuvenescence," CP
- "Remembrances—For D.D.," N
- "Requiem for a Church Condemned," EL
- "Requiescat," N
- "Revery," EL
- "Riddle," F, EL
- "A Rondeau to Dreams," J
- "A Rondeau to Louise," J
- "Safeguards," N
- "Salute to T.L.T.," EL
- "The Savage," J
- "September," CP
- "Seven Days," CP
- "Six Sonnets to the Bridge Club," CP
- "Snow Prayers," F, EL
- "Spring," J
- "The Survivors," F, EL "The Swallows Speak," J "Sword and Spirit," CP
- "Thomason the Historian," EL
- "Three Rabbits," F
- "Three Sonnets to Jones," CP
- "Through the Window," EL
- "Time Worn," EL
- "To a Portrait of Ellen," EL
- "To a Tired Clerk," F, EL
- "To the Bugle Not Blown," F, EL
- "Treason," CP
- "Trinity,'• F, EL
- "Two Children," N
- "Underground," N "Upside Down," N
- "Veterans," CP
- "Warbler," CP
- "The Watchers," EL
- "The Waters Above and Below," CP
- "What Things Endure," N
- "Whence," CP
- "White," N
- "Whose," CP
- "Why," CP
- "Winter Garden," CP
- "Winter Rite," N
- "Wisdom," J
- "Within the Storm," N
- "Words," EL